This is Trigun.
Oh, my God.
You
Don't drink this stuff you
have no tolerance for it.
It's disrespectful to the
booze to drink it like that
I'm impressed.
Hooch's brand name.
Look, we did everything we could.
You've got to stop beating yourself up.
If you have to call it
something, call it destiny.
Don't try to justify it by
labeling it with a simple word.
So many died, and they
won't be coming back.
I can't stand it.
It's more than I can bear.
I killed him.
I killed Brad.
Vash, it wasn't your fault.
I'm sure there was nothing you
could have done to save it.
I'm sorry.
Everyone who touches me ends up dying.
That very well may be, but there's
nothing you can do about it at this point.
You've still got somewhere
else you have to go.
Don't you agree?
I agree.
I'm not done yet.
Whatever it takes, I have to face him.
Ah, there it is
We're here, it's about time!
Yay, team!
I'll have a pudding olive
oil and a mocha frosty cream
Am I correct in assuming
that means you're hungry?
Oh, Mason, how could you tell, Mr.
Wolfwood?
I know absolutely
everything about you, honey.
Well, forget it, dear!
I'm afraid sex supplements
are out of the question.
Nice comeback? Ahah!
Vash?
Yeah, Meryl? What's up?
Uh-oh, um... nothing.
Hello?
Is anybody in there?
Hello!
Who's there?
Where poor, unfortunate, hungry
travelers aimlessly wandering the desert.
Excuse me.
Would it be alright if we came inside?
I'll let you in for three hundred thousand
double dollar three hundred thousand
Exactly.
I said it cuz I know you don't have it.
It's my little way of saying
you're not welcome here
Why the sudden hostility?
We don't mean you any harm.
Yeah,
it's not like we're dangerous or
anything I'm Meryl Stryfe from
the Bernardelli I don't care if
you're from Bernardelli or the feds.
My answer is final.
You're not coming in.
Do you understand?
Hey, you're not being
very fair about this?
Let's go, huh?
How come they don't want us and
we have to respect them the people
of this town probably have a
good reason it's not just a whim!
I can't believe he's just leaving!
Isn't he over it yet?
What
are
you all right?
Now, now, aren't you going to
say thank you to the nice man?
Say thank you. Come on now.
Thank you, sir.
Now that was easy, wasn't it?
Huh?
Hey!
There's only desert that way!
Let's go.
I think we need to take
a little side trip.
Quit standing around wasting time.
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
Anybody home?
What?
Get out!
Get out of here!
Wait! Stop it! We're not bad at you! Hey!
We just got turned away
from that town like you!
Now we just want to stay
here for a little while!
Oh, come on, we won't hurt you, I promise!
Please, just listen to me,
I'm not asking for a favor!
Here, you want a trade?
Pull that away!
Well, I guess this means we have a deal.
Mr.
Wolfwood, those were
our emergency rations.
This is an emergency, isn't it?
I would agree with that.
This is definitely an emergency.
Really?
Well, what do you know, apparently
I seem to be outnumbered this time.
Yay!
Millie, what do you think you're doing?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You want some, too, Meryl?
They're really tasty.
I see.
So these kids are all orphans, huh?
Yeah.
It's really just a coincidence.
It happened by chance.
We all ended up gathering
here in the same place.
It's unusual, but that sort of
thing has been known to happen.
You guys have been a great help, actually.
We didn't have much to eat and
you came in a really good time.
No big deal, just lending a helping hand.
So I was just wondering, why is it
they won't let you into the town?
They won't let any outsiders in,
even if they're only children.
The townsfolk are frightened.
It's as simple as that.
Why?
I'm not sure.
But I do know that every town in
this region has been abandoned.
Well, except for Key Bass over there.
My town was abandoned too the same way.
One day, without warning,
everyone just stopped what they
were doing, and they began to walk.
They didn't take a thing with them, and
they didn't say a word as they laughed.
Dad! Dad! What's wrong? What's the
matter? Say something! What's happening?
What are you all doing? Dad!
Mom! Mom! Dad!
They all just left home, walked out
of town like they were blind and dumb.
They looked like zombies, like
something was controlling them.
All of the others went through
the same thing with their parents.
They all left at the same time.
Tell me one thing.
During the time this was happening,
did you see anyone other
than the townsfolk there?
No, uh-uh.
But actually, I did hear a strange voice.
What did it say?
I still don't understand what it
had to do with them leaving home.
It said this is what you
get for taking so long
It's him
Boy he never does get a
break does he poor sub so
what are you gonna do now
that you're going in or what?
What'd I say?
No kid is ever going to warm up to a guy
that walks around with an empty smile.
Why don't you guys hand that up to me?
I'll be happy to carry it for you.
Let's go.
Did you say something
about kids warming up?
Alright, shut up.
It's just that these guys are
a little bit shy, that's all.
You two are so good, you're
great at helping out.
Thank you very much.
So if you cut it with a
knife along the tendon at a
right angle like this and
sprinkle on a lot of pepper,
it'll actually last a lot
longer than you think.
And guess what, it'll taste better, too.
Really?
Women are a marvel, aren't they?
That's for sure.
Hey there, what you cooking, guys?
That's our secret until supper time. Yeah.
Geez, how could you be so cold?
That guy, he is nothing but trouble.
Dig in, everyone.
Help yourself.
This is delicious.
It's yummy.
It's good.
I like it.
It's kind of wiggly.
This ain't bad either.
You got it, I give it.
Um...
Well, they're all fast asleep at last.
I'm guessing it's a long time
since they were able to relax.
Just look at those happy faces.
Mommy...
Daddy...
If I take too long
they'll make another move!
Still we can't just leave these kids.
Quit being so serious
and cheer up! Come on!
Let's have a drink.
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
What was that?
I heard a gun go off.
Where'd it come from?
I don't know.
Let's go check it out.
Everyone get away from the window!
Why are they shooting him?
I said get away from the window!
Everyone will hang here!
Come all out!
We know you're in there!
If you aren't out here by the time it
comes to ten, we're coming in after you!
And we will shoot to kill!
Well, what's the plan?
The only way out of this
misunderstanding is to reason with them.
Reason with those hotheads?
Are you nuts?
Can't you come up with
anything better than that?
Never mind, I'll go alone.
Three!
Two, one!
Time's up!
Hi, we're not exactly sure what we did
to upset you fellas, we meant no harm.
Would you mind filling us in a little bit?
You're just pretending to be nice to these
kids for camouflage, you piece of trash.
I don't buy you crap for a minute.
I'm really sorry, but I have no
idea what you're talking about.
Don't play dumb with us, spiky boy,
you and your pals are the only
outsiders anywhere near town.
Wait, this is a false alarm.
You didn't do anything!
This is all some kind of terrible mistake!
Oh yeah, you're a real Mr.
Nice Guy, aren't you?
Jeffrey was killed and
he was my best friend!
Stupid bunch of blundering ignoramuses!
Wait, stop!
Give the goody-goody routine
a rest, will you, Vash?
Please, just listen to
what we have to say!
You worthless piece of shit!
You have to hear me out.
What the hell's going on?
Easy, easy, easy!
Oh my god!
The weather's still in here!
Why would they...
Wait a minute, isn't this entire
area made up of solid dead rock?
It would have to be.
It's the only way they
can build a house on it.
I don't understand.
What are they doing here?
Beats the heck out of me.
There's one thing for sure, though.
We're not safe here.
We'll divert their attention.
You two get the kids out.
Okay, understood.
You will let us into your town, won't you?
Well, that takes care of them.
Time for us to get going.
Hey, good luck. Thanks.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
What's the matter?
Can I kill those either?
You can't kill those, no!
Oh, my God!
We always have to do everything your way!
No!
Oh, my God!
What are those things?
Pretty well organized
for ordinary sandworms.
Yeah, I agree.
He's out there, some...
Some rotten lowlife must be sitting back
watching as they do his dirty work for him.
Do you suppose...
How did the worms get inside the town?
Try the building, hurry! Huh?
If you climb high enough, the
worms won't be able to get you!
Right, let's go!
What's wrong? Are you hurt?
Hey, I'm sorry! Come back!
I'm on it.
This is so horrible.
Our whole town's destroyed now.
Where's Millie and the boy?
It's all right.
They're over with Wolfwood.
Yeah, they'll be all right then.
But what is this feeling?
I keep having this strange sensation
like something is out of place.
Too many of them here
Wait!
I caught you fair and square, huh?
It's all right, there's
nothing to be ashamed of.
Damn, ghost.
That's it.
What happened?
You were using a high-frequency
device to control them.
I want to know why.
They're your own people.
Why would you want to hurt them?
Because they're not my people.
Because I am a gung-ho gun!
I'm the fourth of the gung-ho guns.
I'm Zazie the Beast. You're kidding.
Don't cry!
God, that is so annoying.
This confirms why I hate children.
They whine, they get depressed,
and they'll only brush
their teeth when they're
told because they're too
stupid to do otherwise.
They completely lack any
concept of free will!
You probably aren't even capable
of comprehending why I would
choose to do Something this
interesting stop it no hey what
are you doing babe my name is
Zazie it's Zazie the Beast you
know this isn't who you really
are huh it's true I Saw you crying
the other night the demon hasn't
won at one point you even tried
To cheer me on in spite of him
well that's where you're wrong
demons can block their
consciousness And memory on demand I
don't believe that you want it
this way you're forcing yourself
Goody two shoes idiot you don't know who
I am that's fine believe whatever you want
You could just die thinking your pleasant
little thoughts stop this beat right now?
How could you do that?
Why, Wolfwood?
It didn't have to end like this.
Kids are kids, and that's one thing.
This was no kid, he was
nothing but a damn demon.
And if I hadn't shot him,
that would have been you lying there.
But you're wrong.
You wasn't going to shoot me.
I saved your ass yet one more time and you
come after me with your childish bullshit?
You shouldn't have killed him.
You know you're wrong.
What other alternative do I
have if we're going to survive?
We're searching for a place where we
can live our lives in peaceful days.
With no wars and no stealing.
A place that isn't run by fear.
A place where people can live and
actually trust other human beings.
I don't want to hear it!
I don't need to hear your
idealistic dreams right now!
Thank you.
to realize a mistake
to not lie to love one
another to not kill those
are very simple things!
but these times won't
allow for them there is
no green on this planet
even though we want it.
and won it so badly a place where we can
live peaceful days with
no wars nor stealing?
A sacred place where
people can live as people.
Yes, there.
That place is called.